<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NCBA_Project_Program</string>

    <!-- HEADER -->
    <string name="headerStatementOne">Mores et Scientia</string>
    <string name="headerStatementTwo">NATIONAL COLLEGE OF BUSINESS AND ARTS</string>
    <string name="headerStatementThree">Educating Globally Competitive Filipinos</string>

    <!-- 2. ====================== ACADEMIC PROGRAMS ====================== -->
    <string name="academicStatementOne">
        Living up to its founder’s vision, NCBA has opted to remain as a specialized school and its growth measured and steady through the years. From that small edifice along R. Papa St. , NCBA gradually expanded its academic programs and facilities with the purpose of producing for the nation the type of educated manpower it needs for its development and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="academicStatementTwo">
        All the policies, programs and activities of the College are in consonance with its school philosophy, which states that “every individual, regardless of race, creed and age, has the inalienable right to quality education, which is in keeping with his dignity as a human being and which he needs in the attainment of a happy and useful life and in working for unity and peace in the society of man.”
    </string>

    <string name="academicStatementThree">
        In addition, the National College of Business and Arts offers a rich academic program that includes extensive internship opportunities for students interested in pursuing a career in public or private service.
    </string>

    <string name="academicStatementFour">
        Finally, preparing for a career is a vital part of NCBA’s education program. The College’s commitment to quality education was likewise manifested in its training of would-be teachers as evidenced in the yearly high percentage of board exam passers. Graduates of other college courses intending to pursue a career in grade school or high school teaching are also accommodated in NCBA’s education program via the Certificate of Professional Education.
    </string>

    <!-- 2.1. ====================== ACADEMIC PROGRAMS | GRADUATE PROGRAMS ====================== -->
    <string name="graduateStatementOneProgramObjectives">
        In the business world, there are increasing opportunities and competitiveness. At stake are key managerial positions and entrepreneurial possibilities. To those who are competent and qualified there are unlimited potentials. The National College of Business and Arts, aware of these opportunities offers an MBA Program with the following underlying objectives for students:
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStatementTwoProgramObjectives">
        • To develop (whether they are already gainfully employed in business establishments or engaged in their own private business) the entrepreneurial and managerial ability to successfully confront the complex problems of the business world.
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStatementThreeProgramObjectives">
        • To develop critical thinking directed towards action, reduce margin or error in the formulation and implementation of decisions.
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStatementFourProgramObjectives">
        • To develop a real sense of relationship between the economic, spiritual, political, social and technological environment vis a vis the dynamic life of the business firm.
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStatementFiveProgramObjectives">
        • To afford professionals an opportunity to pursue a comprehensive program in business management which includes not only theories, concepts, and techniques in business, as well as its application based on Philippine conditions.
    </string>

    <!-- 2.1.1. ====================== ACADEMIC PROGRAMS | GRADUATE PROGRAMS | MBA ====================== -->
    <string name="graduateStatementMBAFirst">
        The Program offers Plan A (Thesis Program): \n
        •  Basic Course (9 units) \n
        •  Major Course (15 units) \n
        •  Cognate Course (12 units) \n
        •  Thesis (6 units)
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStatementMBASecond">
        Plan B (Non-Thesis Program) \n
        •  Basic Course (9 units) \n
        •  Major Course (15 units) \n
        •  Cognate Course (12 units)
    </string>

    <!-- 2.1.2. ====================== ACADEMIC PROGRAMS | GRADUATE PROGRAMS | MPA ====================== -->
    <string name="graduateStatementMPAFirst">
        The aim of the Master in Public Administration program is to assist one in acquiring the knowledge, competencies, and ethical values necessary to operate effectively in an administrative capacity.
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStatementMPASecond">
        The Program offers Plan A (Thesis Program): \n
        •  Basic Course (9 units) \n
        •  Major Course (15 units) \n
        •  Cognate Course (12 units) \n
        •  Thesis (6 units)
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStatementMPAThird">
        Plan B (Non-Thesis Program) \n
        •  Basic Course (9 units) \n
        •  Major Course (15 units) \n
        •  Cognate Course (12 units)
    </string>

    <!-- 2.2. ====================== ACADEMIC PROGRAMS | COLLEGIATE PROGRAMS ====================== -->
    <string name="collegiateStatementTitleFirst">BS ACCOUNTANCY (BSA) AND BS MANAGEMENT ACCOUNTING (BSMA)</string>
    <string name="collegiateStatementTitleSecond">BS BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION</string>
    <string name="collegiateStatementTitleThird">BS INFORMATION SYSTEM (BSIS) and BS COMPUTER SCIENCE (BSCS)</string>
    <string name="collegiateStatementTitleFourth">BS IN HOSPITALITY MANAGEMENT (BSHM)</string>
    <string name="collegiateStatementTitleFifth">BACHELOR OF ELEMENTARY EDUCATION (BEEd) AND BACHELOR OF SECONDARY EDUCATION (BSED)</string>
    <string name="collegiateStatementTitleSixth">BACHELOR OF ARTS IN ENGLISH LANGUAGE (AB)</string>
</resources>