<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NCBA_Project_Program</string>

    <!-- HEADER -->
    <string name="headerStatementOne">Mores et Scientia</string>
    <string name="headerStatementTwo">NATIONAL COLLEGE OF BUSINESS AND ARTS</string>
    <string name="headerStatementThree">Educating Globally Competitive Filipinos</string>

    <!-- 1. ====================== ABOUT US PROGRAMS ====================== -->
    <!-- 1.1. ====================== ABOUT US PROGRAMS | THE INSTITUTIONS ====================== -->
    <string name="aboutUsTheInstitutionStatementOne">
        As an institution of higher education, we are a teaching and learning community dedicated to the search for truth, the transmission of knowledge, and the appreciation of beauty.
    </string>
    <string name="aboutUsTheInstitutionStatementTwo">
        National College of Business and Arts is committed to the education of the whole person – mind and heart, body and spirit. Our undergraduate programs are built on a core curriculum rooted in the liberal arts and business administration. Our curricula are balanced with career preparation and stress the importance of integrating knowledge, critical thinking, problem solving, communication, and aesthetic appreciation. Our graduate programs concentrate in the areas of professional studies which combine theory and practice. In addition to our academic programs, we are actively engaged with the local community in providing cultural, educational, and professional events.
    </string>
    <string name="aboutUsTheInstitutionStatementThree">
        National College of Business and Arts attracts a student population with a broad range of backgrounds, abilities, and needs. We admit freshman, transferees, and graduate students. Some of our students are working fulltime who choose to study part-time by attending our night classes.
    </string>
    <string name="aboutUsTheInstitutionStatementFour">
        For 50 years, NCBA has demonstrated an ability to adapt to changes in society. We remain flexible and innovative within the context of our mission/vision. Our future actions will remain focused on our commitment to the total development of our students as a whole person and become more involved with the local community. We will continue to renew and improve our programs and services so that our graduates will be well prepared to work in the twenty-first century.
    </string>

    <!-- 1.2. ====================== ABOUT US PROGRAMS | BRIEF HISTORY ====================== -->
    <string name="AboutUsBriefHistoryFirstStatement">
        In 1968, at the corner of R. Papa and Lepanto streets, between the two giants in Philippine private education (University of the East with its mammoth population of 65,000 and Far Eastern University with 47,000 enrollees), a small building was erected to house a small school – National College of Business and Arts (N.C.B.A).
    </string>
    <string name="AboutUsBriefHistorySecondStatement">
        NCBA’s founder was the late Dr. Doroteo S. Pasion, a well-known educator (former Dean of Commerce of San Beda College, former CPA Review Director of the University of the East, and former President of PSBA), lawyer, accountant, author and civic leader. Dr. Pasion launched NCBA as a public service together with four others who believed in the NCBA concept: Col. Rafael Q. Yap-Diangco, Atty. Jose R. Torres, Mrs. Gloria C. Meñez and Mrs. Lourdes L. Sarabia.
    </string>
    <string name="AboutUsBriefHistoryThirdStatement">
        Keeping to its founder’s vision, NCBA opted to remain as a specialized school and its growth sustained and steady through the years. From a small edifice along R. Papa Street, NCBA slowly expanded its academic programs and facilities with the single purpose of producing for the Nation the type of educated manpower it needs for national development.
    </string>
    <string name="AboutUsBriefHistoryFourthStatement">
        When NCBA opened in 1968, its initial offerings were limited to the following courses: Bachelor of Science in Business Administration; Bachelor of Arts; a two-year course in Secretarial Administration; and its own CPA Review. The High School department was opened in School Year 1973-1974, followed by its additional offerings of short terminal courses in Cooperative; Salesmanship; Bookkeeping and Accounting; and Small Business Management in School Year 1974-1975.
    </string>
    <string name="AboutUsBriefHistoryFifthStatement">
        Today, NCBA has a total of three campuses (Cubao, Taytay and Fairview) and boasts of a complete package of academic offerings from K-12 school to an expanded tertiary education program and graduate courses.
    </string>
    <string name="AboutUsBriefHistorySixthStatement">
        The three campuses of NCBA are PACUCOA accredited for its BSBA program to attest that the College has formal recognition of an educational program possessing high level of quality based on the analysis of the merits of its educational operations in attaining its objectives and its role in the community that it serves.
    </string>
    <string name="AboutUsBriefHistorySeventhStatement">
        Since its founding, NCBA has endeavored continually to perpetuate its educational policy to offer and provide both facilities and teaching force, a complete education for young men and women and equip them with the skills and training to become responsible citizens and future leaders of the country.
    </string>

    <!-- 1.3. ====================== ABOUT US PROGRAMS | VISION, MISSION AND CORE VALUES ====================== -->
    <!-- 1.4. ====================== ABOUT US PROGRAMS | NCBA HYMN ====================== -->
    <string name="AboutUsNCBAHymnFirstStatement">
        Let’s stand erect, we’re proud that we are one\n
        We will stay through the rain and sunshine!\n
        Sing and sing the world will hear\n
        The name we hold so very dear
    </string>

    <string name="AboutUsNCBAHymnSecondStatement">
        N.C.B.A. Thy name shall ever live\n
        Thy fame and greatness forever.\n
        Shine, shine as a brilliant star\n
        Shine brightly evermore
    </string>

    <string name="AboutUsNCBAHymnThirdStatement">
        If your light shall ever become dim\n
        We will stand beside thee as men\n
        N.C.B.A.  N.C.B.A.\n
        Thy name shall ever stay
    </string>

    <string name="AboutUsNCBAHymnFourthStatment">
        Let’s stand erect, we’re proud that we are one\n
        We will stay through the rain and sunshine!\n
        Sing and sing the world will hear\n
        The name we hold so very dear
    </string>

    <string name="AboutUsNCBAHymnFifthStatment">
        N.C.B.A.  Thy name shall ever live\n
        Thy fame and greatness forever.\n
        Shine, shine as a brilliant star\n
        Shine brightly evermore
    </string>

    <string name="AboutUsNCBAHymnSixthStatment">
        If your light shall ever become dim\n
        We will stand beside thee as men\n
        N.C.B.A.  N.C.B.A.\n
        Thy name shall ever stay\n
        HURRAY!!!
    </string>




    <!-- 2. ====================== ACADEMIC PROGRAMS ====================== -->
    <string name="academicStatementOne">
        Living up to its founder’s vision, NCBA has opted to remain as a specialized school and its growth measured and steady through the years. From that small edifice along R. Papa St. , NCBA gradually expanded its academic programs and facilities with the purpose of producing for the nation the type of educated manpower it needs for its development and well-being.
    </string>

    <string name="academicStatementTwo">
        All the policies, programs and activities of the College are in consonance with its school philosophy, which states that “every individual, regardless of race, creed and age, has the inalienable right to quality education, which is in keeping with his dignity as a human being and which he needs in the attainment of a happy and useful life and in working for unity and peace in the society of man.”
    </string>

    <string name="academicStatementThree">
        In addition, the National College of Business and Arts offers a rich academic program that includes extensive internship opportunities for students interested in pursuing a career in public or private service.
    </string>

    <string name="academicStatementFour">
        Finally, preparing for a career is a vital part of NCBA’s education program. The College’s commitment to quality education was likewise manifested in its training of would-be teachers as evidenced in the yearly high percentage of board exam passers. Graduates of other college courses intending to pursue a career in grade school or high school teaching are also accommodated in NCBA’s education program via the Certificate of Professional Education.
    </string>

    <!-- 2.1. ====================== ACADEMIC PROGRAMS | GRADUATE PROGRAMS ====================== -->
    <string name="graduateStatementOneProgramObjectives">
        In the business world, there are increasing opportunities and competitiveness. At stake are key managerial positions and entrepreneurial possibilities. To those who are competent and qualified there are unlimited potentials. The National College of Business and Arts, aware of these opportunities offers an MBA Program with the following underlying objectives for students:
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStatementTwoProgramObjectives">
        • To develop (whether they are already gainfully employed in business establishments or engaged in their own private business) the entrepreneurial and managerial ability to successfully confront the complex problems of the business world.
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStatementThreeProgramObjectives">
        • To develop critical thinking directed towards action, reduce margin or error in the formulation and implementation of decisions.
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStatementFourProgramObjectives">
        • To develop a real sense of relationship between the economic, spiritual, political, social and technological environment vis a vis the dynamic life of the business firm.
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStatementFiveProgramObjectives">
        • To afford professionals an opportunity to pursue a comprehensive program in business management which includes not only theories, concepts, and techniques in business, as well as its application based on Philippine conditions.
    </string>

    <!-- 2.1.1. ====================== ACADEMIC PROGRAMS | GRADUATE PROGRAMS | MBA ====================== -->
    <string name="graduateStatementMBAFirst">
        The Program offers Plan A (Thesis Program): \n
        •  Basic Course (9 units) \n
        •  Major Course (15 units) \n
        •  Cognate Course (12 units) \n
        •  Thesis (6 units)
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStatementMBASecond">
        Plan B (Non-Thesis Program) \n
        •  Basic Course (9 units) \n
        •  Major Course (15 units) \n
        •  Cognate Course (12 units)
    </string>

    <!-- 2.1.2. ====================== ACADEMIC PROGRAMS | GRADUATE PROGRAMS | MPA ====================== -->
    <string name="graduateStatementMPAFirst">
        The aim of the Master in Public Administration program is to assist one in acquiring the knowledge, competencies, and ethical values necessary to operate effectively in an administrative capacity.
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStatementMPASecond">
        The Program offers Plan A (Thesis Program): \n
        •  Basic Course (9 units) \n
        •  Major Course (15 units) \n
        •  Cognate Course (12 units) \n
        •  Thesis (6 units)
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStatementMPAThird">
        Plan B (Non-Thesis Program) \n
        •  Basic Course (9 units) \n
        •  Major Course (15 units) \n
        •  Cognate Course (12 units)
    </string>

    <!-- 2.2.1. ====================== ACADEMIC PROGRAMS | COLLEGIATE PROGRAMS | ACCOUNTING ====================== -->
    <string name="collegiateStatementOneAccounting">
        Our curriculum is designed to provide students with the technical accounting knowledge and skills, and with the integration of professional values and work ethics that are essential to meet the rapidly changing demands and challenges of the accounting profession.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementTwoAccounting">
        Accounting continues to be a field with one of the highest demands for graduates. To meet this demand, the program has the following objectives:
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementThreeAccounting">
        •  Provide students with the knowledge and tools needed to obtain meaningful employment and have successful career in the accounting field.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementFourAccounting">
        •  Employ critical-thinking, analytical, and problem-solving skills to resolve complex business and accounting issues.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementFiveAccounting">
        •  Provide students the educational requirements of various professional accounting certification examinations.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementSixAccounting">
        •  Identify the appropriate managerial and business issues critical in analyzing accounting data and other information used for identifying and assessing opportunities and risks, developing organizational plans, allocating resources, and accomplishing objectives.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementSevenAccounting">
        •  Apply relevant accounting principles and standards to specific business activities and workplace situations.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementEightAccounting">
        •  Employ national, international, and historical perspectives to analyze accounting and business issues.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementNineAccounting">
        •  Identify ethical issues associated with accounting and business situations and apply appropriate principles of ethics and civic responsibility.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementTenAccounting">
        •  Use analytical and research tools to monitor evolving accounting standards and practices and to maintain professional skills in a changing business environment.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementElevenAccounting">
        •  Apply the interpersonal and leadership skills expected of today’s accounting professional.
    </string>


    <!-- 2.2.2. ====================== ACADEMIC PROGRAMS | COLLEGIATE PROGRAMS | BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION ====================== -->
    <string name="collegiateStatementOneBusinessAd">
        •  This program of study is an integration of the basic business, core business and professional courses that are geared towards developing our students to become effective business leaders in the future. The program’s thrust is to focus their study in one of the four areas, namely: Human Resource Development Management, Financial Management, Marketing Management and Operations Management.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementTwoBusinessAd">
        •  Upon completion of the program, our students can successfully pursue careers in the public and private sectors. This degree program is also designed to complement the graduate business programs such as, Masters in Business Administration (M.B.A.).
    </string>

    <!-- 2.2.3. ====================== ACADEMIC PROGRAMS | COLLEGIATE PROGRAMS | COMPUTER SCIENCE ====================== -->
    <string name="collegiateStatementOneComputerScience">
        The BSIS/BSCS degree programs aim to produce Information Technology (IT) professionals with specialized skills catering to the needs of the I.T. industry. These programs primarily cover a wide range of learning that includes Computer Programming using different kinds of computer programming languages from 2nd Generation to 3rd Generation’s Object Oriented Programming; Systems Analysis and Design, Object Oriented Analysis tool for the improvement of business Information System; Sofware Engineering and systems integration into a multi-platform environment.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementTwoComputerScience">
        The program aims to develop its students with the appropriate industry standards closed and open source systems and enough skills in application-oriented environment, Integrated Development Environment Web Application programming with integration of Content Management Systems(CMS) via open source implementation, large scale database development, networking application and administration in a multi and crossed platform environment, and network planning and managements.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementThreeComputerScience">
        While the course of practice is done independently, there are numerous opportunities to develop teamwork skills with group based projects throughtout the course. The students will apply their knowledge in academic theory and system development by completing an industry-based project in order to expose and train them to work in a professional environment.
    </string>



    <string name="collegiateStatementFourComputerScience">
        Computer science programs integrate practical learning in various ways to ensure students gain hands-on experience and develop real-world skills. By incorporating these practical learning opportunities into the curriculum, computer science programs ensure that students not only grasp theoretical concepts but also develop the skills, confidence, and adaptability needed to succeed in the dynamic field of computing.
    </string>


    <string name="collegiateStatementFiveComputerScience">
        A computer science program provides a comprehensive curriculum to prepare students for careers in technology and computing. It covers theoretical knowledge and practical skills, preparing students for diverse opportunities in fields like Software Engineering. Cybersecurity, Artificial Intelligence, and Programming Languages.
    </string>


    <string name="collegiateStatementSixComputerScience">
        Computer Science covers a wide range of key areas of study, each essential for understanding and working in the field of computing and the field continues to evolve with advancements in technology and new research areas emerging over time.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementSevenComputerScience">
        Some of the following areas focuses on Theory Computation, Data Structures and Algorithm, Distributed Systems and Cloud Computing.
    </string>


    <string name="collegiateStatementEightComputerScience">
        Computer Science program equips graduates for success both locally and globally by providing them with a robust skill set, adaptable mindset, and a deep understanding of foundational principles that transcend geographical boundaries.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementNineComputerScience">
        By equipping graduates with technical expertise, problem-solving skills, cross-cultural communication abilities, adaptability, ethical awareness, and a global perspective, Computer Science programs prepare them to thrive in a rapidly changing world, whether they pursue opportunities in their local communities or embark on global careers.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementTenComputerScience">
        Information systems programs integrate practical learning in several ways to provide students with hands-on experience and prepare them for careers in the field. By integrating practical learning opportunities into the curriculum, information systems programs ensure that students not only understand theoretical concepts but also gain the hands-on experience and practical skills necessary to succeed in the field of information systems.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementElevenComputerScience">
        Information systems program provides students with a solid foundation in both technical and business aspects of information technology, preparing them for careers in areas such as business analysis, systems analysis, project management, information security, and database administration. Its multidisciplinary curriculum covers Business Analysis, System Design, Database Management, and Data Analytics.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementTwelveComputerScience">
        Information Systems program covers a diverse range of key areas that integrate business knowledge with technology solutions. These key areas of study in Information Systems prepare students for careers in areas such as Enterprise System, Information Security and Risk Management, IT consulting, IT Governance and compliance, where they can leverage technology to support organizational objectives and drive innovation.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementThirteenComputerScience">
        Information Systems program equips graduates for success in both local and global contexts by providing them with a blend of technical, business, and interpersonal skills that are highly valued in today\'s interconnected world with a combination of technical expertise, business acumen, cross-cultural communication abilities, and a global perspective, Information Systems programs prepare them to succeed in a variety of roles and industries, both locally and on the global stage.
    </string>


    <!-- 2.2.4. ====================== ACADEMIC PROGRAMS | COLLEGIATE PROGRAMS | HOSPITALITY MANAGEMENT ====================== -->
    <string name="collegiateStatementOneHospitalityManagement">
        The BSHM program offers competitive and industry-based curriculum that provides the students with the required competencies and positive work values needed to meet the demands of the changing industry and global environment. The program also provides the students with practical alternative learning through various skills development activities, seminars and educational tours. Likewise, the program aims to provide the Hotel and Restaurant industry with graduates who possess the requisite knowledge, skills and values to become successful entrepreneurs.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementTwoHospitalityManagement">
        • To provide students with a strong management and service orientation, as well as global perspective of the hotel and restaurant operations.
    </string>

    <string name="collegiateStatementThreeHospitalityManagement">
        • Provide students the necessary knowledge and skills needed to develop the competencies required in order to prepare them for gainful employment within the service industry both locally and abroad.
    </string>


    <!-- 2.2.5. ====================== ACADEMIC PROGRAMS | COLLEGIATE PROGRAMS | ELEMENTARY EDUCATION ====================== -->
    <string name="collegiateStatementOneElementaryEducation">
        The Education curriculum aims to equip future teachers with a wide range of theoretical and methodological skills that are important for a more innovative approach to teaching in order to maximize student learning.
    </string>


    <!-- 2.2.6. ====================== ACADEMIC PROGRAMS | COLLEGIATE PROGRAMS | ENGLISH LANGUAGE ====================== -->
    <string name="collegiateStatementOneEnglishLanguage">
        Our program focuses on basic skills development for effective communication as well as developing a deeper appreciation for various literary works.
    </string>


    <!-- 2.3.1. ====================== ACADEMIC PROGRAMS | COLLEGIATE PROGRAMS | ENGLISH LANGUAGE ====================== -->
    <string name="programOfferingsStatementOneCollegiateProgram">
        • Bachelor of Science in Accountancy (BSA)\n• Bachelor of Science in Management Accounting (BSMA)\n• Bachelor of Science in Hospitality Management (BSHM)\n• Bachelor of Science in Business Administration (BSBA) major in:
    </string>

    <string name="programOfferingsStatementTwoCollegiateProgram">
        • Human Resource Management\n• Financial Management\n• Marketing Management\n• Operations Management
    </string>

    <string name="programOfferingsStatementThreeCollegiateProgram">
        • Bachelor of Science in Information System (BSIS) – Cubao &amp; Fairview campus only\n• Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (BSCS) – Taytay campus only\n• Bachelor of Arts (AB) in English Language – Fairview &amp; Taytay campus only\n• Bachelor of Elementary Education (BEEd)\n• Bachelor of Secondary Education (BSEd) with specialization in:
    </string>







    <string name="collegiateStatementTitleSecond">BS BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION</string>
    <string name="collegiateStatementTitleThird">BS INFORMATION SYSTEM (BSIS) and BS COMPUTER SCIENCE (BSCS)</string>
    <string name="collegiateStatementTitleFourth">BS IN HOSPITALITY MANAGEMENT (BSHM)</string>
    <string name="collegiateStatementTitleFifth">BACHELOR OF ELEMENTARY EDUCATION (BEEd) AND BACHELOR OF SECONDARY EDUCATION (BSED)</string>
    <string name="collegiateStatementTitleSixth">BACHELOR OF ARTS IN ENGLISH LANGUAGE (AB)</string>

    <!-- 3.1. ====================== ADMISSION PROGRAMS | PAYMENT OPTIONS ====================== -->
    <string name="paymentOptionsStatementOne">
        Please be informed that at present, only payments made at the Finance Office of your respective NCBA Campus will be accepted. Until further notice, we have discontinued receiving payments via bank transfers or over the counter bank transactions.
    </string>

    <string name="paymentOptionsStatementTwo">
        Please contact the Finance Office for queries. Thank you for your cooperation.
    </string>

    <!-- 3.2. ====================== ADMISSION PROGRAMS | ENROLLMENT PROCEDURES ====================== -->
    <!-- 3.3. ====================== ADMISSION PROGRAMS | GRADUATE STUDIES ADMISSION ====================== -->
    <string name="graduateStudiesStatementOne">
        Admission is open to holders of a bachelor’s degree in any field of discipline from a college/university.  Applicants must satisfactorily complete the admission requirements for graduate study as shown below:
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStudiesStatementTwo">
        • Certificate of Transfer Credential\n• Birth Certificate – original and photocopy\n• Recommendation letters\n• 2 pcs 2×2 ID picture\n• 2 pcs letter envelope with stamps (long)
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStudiesStatementThree">
        • Certificate of Transfer Credential\n• Scholastic Record / Certificate of Grades\n• Birth Certificate – original and photocopy\n• 2 Recommendation letters\n• 2 pcs 2×2 ID picture\n• 2 pcs letter envelope with stamps (long)
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStudiesStatementFour">
        • Permit to Cross-enroll\n• 2 pcs 2×2 ID picture\n• 2 pcs letter envelope with stamps (long)
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStudiesStatementFive">
        A graduate student will be eligible for the awarding of an MBA/MPA degree upon satisfactory completion of the following:
    </string>

    <string name="graduateStudiesStatementSix">
        • Completion of the basic, major and cognate courses as prescribed in the curriculum\n• A final grade of at least 2.0 in all courses taken\n• Passing of the comprehensive exam\n• Passing of the panel oral defense (for Thesis program)\n• Minimum residency of two (2) trimesters or must have earned at least twenty four (24) units of credit from NCBA
    </string>


    <!-- 3.4. ====================== ADMISSION PROGRAMS | COLLEGE ADMISSION ====================== -->
    <string name="collegeStatementOne">
        Admission is open to all Senior High School graduates who meet all the requirements necessary for registration.
    </string>

    <string name="collegeStatementTwo">
        • Report Card (Form 138 / SF 10)\n• Certificate of Good Moral Character\n• Birth Certificate – original and photocopy\n• 2 pcs 2×2 ID picture\n• 2 pcs letter envelope (long) with stamps
    </string>

    <string name="collegeStatementThree">
        • Certificate of Transfer Credential\n• Scholastic Record / Certificate of Grades\n• Certificate of Good Moral Character\n• Birth Certificate – original and photocopy\n• 2 pcs 2×2 ID picture\n• 2 pcs letter envelope (long) with stamps
    </string>

    <string name="collegeStatementFour">
        • Permit to Cross-enroll\n• Certificate of Good Moral Character (if cross-enrollee from another school)\n• 2 pcs 2×2 ID picture\n• 2 pcs letter envelope (long) with stamps
    </string>


    <!-- 3.5. ====================== ADMISSION PROGRAMS | SCHOLARSHIPS AND DISCOUNTS ====================== -->
    <string name="scholarshipDiscountsFirstStatement">
        Entrance scholarship is given to elementary and senior high school (SHS) graduates who obtained an academic excellence award of With Highest Honor (98-100%) &amp; graduated from a class of not less than fifty (50) students.
    </string>

    <string name="scholarshipDiscountsSecondStatement">
        For bonafide students with a General Weighted Average (GWA) of not lower than 1.20 and 1.30 and must:
    </string>

    <string name="scholarshipDiscountsThirdStatement">
        • Be enrolled in full load of academic units as prescribed in the curriculum;\n• Have no grade lower than 2.0 for full scholar and 2.5 for partial scholar in any academic and/or non-academic courses;\n• Have no “dropped” remark in any course previously enrolled
    </string>

    <string name="scholarshipDiscountsFourthStatement">
        To apply for a scholarship, pls go to the Registrar’s Office for processing of your application. Deadline for submission is on the last day of enrollment.
    </string>

    <string name="scholarshipDiscountsFifthStatement">
        In accordance with the existing guidelines as provided for under PD #577, scholarship is granted to the dependants of military personnel.
    </string>

    <string name="scholarshipDiscountsSixthStatement">
        Other government funded scholarships provided by the PVAO, CHED, DEPED and LGUs are also available for eligible applicants.
    </string>

    <string name="scholarshipDiscountsSeventhStatement">
        To apply for a scholarship, pls go to the Registrar’s Office for processing of your application. Deadline for submission is on the last day of enrollment.
    </string>

    <string name="scholarshipDiscountsEightStatement">
        Incentives are given to families with at least three siblings simultaneously enrolled at NCBA. Incentives are in the form of credit adjustments applied on the student accounts.
    </string>



    <!-- 3.6. ====================== ADMISSION PROGRAMS | CREDENTIALS ====================== -->
    <string name="credentialsFirstStatement">
        • Get an application form at the Registrar’s Office and fill it out completely.\n• Secure clearance from the Registrar’s Office, Finance and Library.\n• Pay the corresponding fee/s at the Finance Office.\n• Present your official receipt at the Registrar’s Office to get a claim stub.
    </string>

    <string name="credentialsSecondStatement">
        For those working or living abroad, the owner of the record must provide an authorization letter to his/her designated representative who will be responsible for applying in his/her behalf. The letter must indicate the following information:
    </string>

    <string name="credentialsThirdStatement">
        • Identity and personal circumstances of the owner of the record, including but not limited to, name, date of birth, course/program, period of stay in school, date of graduation, if applicable.\n• Complete name of the representative and the relationship to the owner of the record.\n• Specify document being applied for, number of copies and purpose for the document /s sought.
    </string>

    <string name="credentialsFourthStatement">
        Both owner of the record and the representative must present sufficient proof of identity by presenting signed copies of at least two valid IDs when applying for any type of document.
    </string>


    <string name="credentialsTwoFirstStatement">
        PROCEDURES IN FILING AN APPLICATION FOR A CORRECTION OF NAME, DATE OF BIRTH, PLACE OF BIRTH OR OTHER PERTINENT INFORMATION
    </string>

    <string name="credentialsTwoSecondStatement">
        As a general rule, all information contained in a student’s record including but not limited to, permanent record (Form 137), high school report card (Form 138), transcript of record, scholastic record, transfer credential and diploma must conform to the birth certificate issued by the Philippine Statistice Authority (PSA), formerly the National Statistics Office (NSO). Should there be any discrepancy, the information found in the birth certificate shall prevail.
    </string>

    <string name="credentialsTwoThirdStatement">
        If there is a discrepancy, the school record can be corrected by filing a notarized affidavit with the Office of the Registrar. The required documents to be submitted include:
    </string>

    <string name="credentialsTwoFourthStatement">
        • Letter of Request (form is available at the Registrar ‘s office)\n• Personal affidavit\n• Affidavit from two disinterested persons – this involves people who know the student personally, but are not related to him/her.
    </string>

    <string name="credentialsTwoFifthStatement">
        However, for those who will opt to change/correct their birth certificate, they must file the appropriate application with the municipal court. The final decision of the court on the applicant‘s petition shall be the basis if any correction is to be made with the school record.
    </string>
</resources>